欢迎各位收看"伟大的发明"
Welcome, everybody! Welcome to Amazing Discoveries!
又播出了
Oh, oh! It's on again!
同志们  能别看吗
Guys, could we please not watch this?
你是否遇过这种情形
Folks, has this ever happened to you?
你正打算去冰箱拿一杯牛奶...
You go to the refrigerator to get a nice glass of milk,
但却打不开纸盒子
...and these cartons are so flinging, flanging hard to open!
天啊  你说对了  麦克
Oh, you said it, Mike.
-一定得有更好的办法  -的确有  凯文
- Aw! There's gotta be a better way. - And there is, Kevin!
-能关掉吗  -不行  凯文
- Can we please turn this off? - No way, Kevin!
有个新产品能保证...
There is a revolutionary new product that guarantees...
你再也不用费力打开牛奶纸盒呢?
... you'll never have to open up milk cartons again?
请看牛奶大师2000
Meet the Milkmaster 2000!
你感兴趣了吧
Are you intrigued?
是啊  说得我心痒痒的
You're flinging, flanging right I am!
记住  这是他第一次使用
Keep in mind, he's never used this product before,
可见这玩意用起来有多容易
you'll see how easy this is to do.
-任何牛奶纸盒都适用  -真简单!
- Go ahead, this works in any milk carton. - Wow, it is easy!
这样我就可以天天喝牛奶了
Now I can have milk every day.
或许你希望我转过去
Perhaps, you would like me to turn like this,
这样就能靠在我背上亲热了
so you can bunny-bump against my back?
老兄 怎么了
Hey, man. What's up?
或许该由你来告诉我吧
Maybe you can tell me.
我的经纪人问我
My agent would want to know
今天为何没有参加我根本不知道的试镜
why I didn't show up at the audition I didn't know I had today.
这几周来她为我争取到的第一个好机会
The first good thing she gets me in weeks.
你怎么没转告我
How could you not give me the message?!
告诉你  我虽然喜欢恶作剧
I'll tell you, I do enjoy guilt...
但不是我干的
... but it wasn't me.
是的  就是他干的没错
Yes, it was. It was him!
好吧  是我干的
Okay, it was me!
怎么会是你
How was it you?
因为当时情况紧急  你知道吗
Well, it was this, it was all so crazy, you know?
钱德在小房间里  倒数十秒
I mean, Chandler was in the closet, counting to 10...
已经数到七了  可我一直找不到地方躲
...and he was up to 7 and I hadn't found a place to hide yet.
我本想告诉你个  都写在手上了
I meant to tell you, and I wrote it all down on my hand.
看  全都在这儿
See? All of it.
是啊  就是我的试镜
Yep, that's my audition.
看吧  这就是我到处放便条纸的原因
See? Now, this is why I keep notepads everywhere.
是啊  所以我们从不叫你一起玩
Yep. And that's why we don't invite you to play.
这有什么了不起的
What is the great tragedy here?
再约个时间呗
You go get yourself another appointment.
艾丝特尔试过了
Well, Estelle tried, you know.
导演说我已经错过了机会
The casting director told her I missed my chance.
这样太不公平了
Oh, that is unfair!
我来打给她  告诉她都是我的错
I'll call her and I'll tell her it was totally my fault.
没用的  导演是不可能
Pheebes, you can't do that. The casting director doesn't
跟演员的朋友谈的
talk to friends.
她只跟经纪人谈
She only talks to agents.
她的生活圈子真是小得可怜啊
What a sad little life she must lead.
好吧
Okay.
-你在做什么  -我心里有数
- What are you doing? - No, I know, I know.
我是菲比·布菲公司的凯特琳
Hi, this is Caitlin from Phoebe Buffay's office.
菲比可以和安谈一谈吗
Is Anne there for Phoebe?
她知道是什么事
She'll know what it's about.
挂电话  快挂...
Hang up. Hang up right
安妮  你好
Annie? Hi.
听着  乔伊·崔比安尼遇到了点小问题
Listen, we've got a problem with Joey Tribbiani.
很显然  他错过了试演
Apparently, he missed his audition.
请问你转告了我们公司的哪一位
Who did you speak to in my office?
艾丝特尔  我真不知该拿她怎么办
Estelle? I don't know what to do with her.
就算她丈夫离她而去  还放火烧了房子
All right, so your husband leaves and burns down the apartment.
没了她  地球照转
The world doesn't stop.
还有谁觉得毛骨悚然
Is anybody else scared?
如果乔伊错过了这次试镜
Right, well look, if Joey loses this audition,
那我就开了艾丝特尔  我管不了那么多
then that is it for Estelle. I don't care!
安妮  你真善良
Annie, you are a doll.
你何时能见他  给我一支笔  笔
What time can you see him? I need a pen. Pen!
快给这女人弄张便条  给她张便条  便条
Get the woman a pad! Get the woman a pad! A pad! A pad!
你现在需要便条了啊
Oh, now you want a pad.
我的小伙子来了
There's my boy?
我的小伙子在这儿
Here's my boy!
还有他的芭比娃娃
And here's his Barbie!
我儿子为什么会玩芭比娃娃
What's uh, what's my boy doing with a Barbie?
他自己在玩具店选的  他很喜欢呢
He picked it out of the toy store himself. He loves it.
他去哪儿都带着
He carries it everywhere,
就像能给他安全感的小毯子
it's like a security blanket.
只不过穿着雪靴和时髦的法国帽
But with ski boots and a kicky beret.
是啊  是很可爱
Yeah, it's cute.
可他为何要玩这个东西
Why does he have it again?
他玩洋娃娃  那又怎样
So he's got a doll. So what?
除非你怕他将来长大后...
Unless you're afraid he's gonna grow up...
进军娱乐行业
...to be in show business.
这与他被两个女人扶养长大
This doesn't have anything to do with the fact
一点关系都没有  是吧
that he is being raised by two women, does it?
好吧  如果你们能接受他抱着芭比
You know what? It's fine. If you're okay with the Barbie thing,
我无所谓
so am I.
把芭比给爸爸  把芭比给我
Give Daddy the Barbie. Ben, give me the Barbie.
你要不要玩一玩怪兽车
Okay, how about. Don't you wanna play with a monster truck?
不要  好吧
No? Okay.
那恐龙士兵怎么样
How about a Dino-Soldier?
罗斯  你真可悲
Ross, You are so pathetic.
为什么不让你的儿子玩洋娃娃
Why can't your son just play with his doll?
我要去上班了
I gotta go to work.
有人看到我左胸的胸垫了吗
Has anybody seen my left boob?
我喜欢那部电影
I loved that movie.
在这里  乔伊  你在干嘛
Here it is. Joey, what are you doing?
对不起  这样比较舒服
I'm sorry. It just felt nice.
乔  乔  接电话
Joe, Joe. Answer the phone.
我只有一只手  你应该关爱残障人士
I only got one good arm. You should be doing stuff for me.
帮我拿件毛衣来
Now, get me a sweater.
快点接啦  是珍妮斯
Just do it! Okay, It's Janice.
如果我接了  今晚就得跟她见面
And if I get it, I'm going to have to see her tonight.
好极了  我今晚得跟她见面了
Oh, that's great. I'll have to see her tonight.
有什么了不起的  你为什么不想见她
What's the big deal? Why don't you want to see Janice?
昨晚我们一起吃晚餐  上菜的时候...
Okay, last night at dinner, when the meals came...
她把一半鸡肉放到我盘里
she put half her chicken piccata on my plate
还拿走了我的番茄
and then she took all my tomatoes.
你觉得这样不好  是因为...
And that's bad because...
你不喜欢吃鸡肉
you hate chicken piccata?
不是
No.
你不想把番茄分给人家
You didn't want to share your tomatoes.
因为番茄对你很重要
Tomatoes are very important to you.
不  因为突然间  我们就成"情侣"了
No, it's like all of the sudden, we were this "couple." Okay?
然后我脑袋里的警报开始大响
And this alarm started going off in my head, you know,
"为了你的人生  快跑快离开这栋大楼!"
"Run for your life! Get out of the building!"
男人真是令人难以置信
Men are unbelievable.
你们这些人是怎么回事
What is it with you people?
心中一旦产生感情就要马上逃开
I mean, the minute you start to feel something, you have to run away?
我知道  那就是...
I know. That...
就是我今晚不想去的原因
That's why I don't want to go tonight.
我怕自己说出一些蠢话
I'm afraid I'm going to say something stupid.
你是说男人那套故意冷漠  保持距离
You mean that "guy thing" where you act mean and distant...
直到我们跟你们分手
until you get us to break up with you?
嘿  你知道这招
Hey, you know about that?
我该怎么做  我想克服它
Look what do I do? I wanna get past this.
我不想再害怕承诺
I don't want to be afraid of the commitment thing.
我想穿过隧道到达胜利的彼岸
I want to go through the tunnel to the other side!
就是指不再害怕承诺
Where there's no fear of commitment.
你们有没有
Do we have any...
你们有什么办法吗
Do we have any thoughts here?
我没穿过那种隧道啦
Well, I've never been through the tunnel myself...
因为据我所知
'cause as I understand it,
车里多于一个女生
you're not allowed to go through
是不能通过隧道的  对吧
with more than one girl in the car, right.
但我想这和战胜其他问题
But it seems to me it's pretty much
是一个道理  直面恐惧
like anything else, you know. Face your fear.
你怕高的话  就站到大楼顶上
You have a fear of heights? You go to the top of the building.
如果你怕虫子
You're afraid of bugs.
就去捉只虫玩玩
Get a bug.
你的情况是害怕承诺...
In this case, you have a fear of commitment.
那你就按时赴约
So I say you go in there
做最勇于承诺的男人
and you be the most committed guy there ever was!
令人惊讶的是  说的还真有道理
Amazingly, that makes sense.
-你这么觉得  -是啊  快去吧  老兄
- You think? - Oh, yeah! Go for it, man!
从高处跳水
Jump off the high dive!
直面枪口  在风中撒尿
Stare down the barrel of the gun! Pee into the wind!
乔  我向你保证
Yeah, Joe, I assure you
如果让我直面枪口...
if I'm staring down the barrel of a gun,
我大概已经尿得到处都是了
I'm gonna be pretty much peeing every which way.
是你今早的面试  我能再用下电话吗
Oh, it's your audition from this morning! Can l use the phone, again?
当然  菲比  电话不就是用来打的吗
Sure, Pheebs, you know, that's what it's there for.
紧急事件及冒牌经纪人专用
Emergencies and pretend agents.
快  宝贝
Come on, baby! Come on!
菲比·布菲要回复呼叫
Hi. I have Phoebe Buffay returning a page.
她在车里  我帮你接过去
Okay, she's in her car. I'll have to patch you through.
演得好极了
Very nice touch.
好的接通了
Okay, go ahead.
说啊  说啊
Talk, talk, talk!
安妮 你好
Hi, Annie?
太好了 你成功了
Fantastic. You got it!
你问我他是否能接受最低工资  这我可不知道
Will he work for scale, you ask me? Well, I don't know about that.
其实我知道  而且他也愿意
Except that I do and he will.
太好了  你人真好
Great. Oh, you are such a sweetheart.
我很愿意与你共进午餐
I would love to have lunch with you!
不如就下个...
How about we have lunch next
过隧道没信号了
Went through a tunnel.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
太感谢你了
Oh, thank you so much!
真有趣  我从未用过汽车电话
It was really fun. I mean, I've never talked on a car phone before.
你真了不起  你能不能帮我个大忙
You are so amazing! Could you just do me this huge favor?
还有个试镜我很想参加
You see, there's another audition I really really want,
但艾丝特尔不愿帮我安排
and Estelle couldn't get me in.
我不知道  一次还挺好玩的  但...
Oh, I don't know. I mean, it was fun one time, but...
拜托  就最后一次行吗
Come on, Please? It would just be this one more.
好吧  其实是最后两次
Well, actually it's two.
两次
Two?
好啦  其实是三次
Yeah, well, really it's three.
拜托  你这么厉害  我爱你
Please? You're so good at it. I love you.
好吧  就这三次  好吗
Okay. But just these three, right?
不  四次
No, it's four.
你今天怎么会想在家吃
So how come you wanted to eat in tonight?
因为我想
Because I wanted to uh...
送你这个东西
...to give you this.
你真是可爱呢
Are you a puppy!
装饰贴纸
Contact paper!
一位炮友送你装饰贴纸...
I never really know what to say when someone you're sleeping with...
你该说什么好呢
gives you contact paper?
等等  还有  这贴纸是贴在
Wait, there's more. See, the contact paper is to go in...
你的新抽屉里的
in your brand new drawer!
看  这抽屉正好能塞进我的梳妆台里
See, the drawer actually goes in my dresser.
你不用这么做的
You didn't have to do this.
不  我要这么做
Yes, I did.
我要这么做  因为你是我的女朋友
Yes, I did. Because you're my girlfriend...
而女朋友就该得到这些
and that's what girlfriends should get.
我得求救兵了...
Well, I gotta buy a vowel...
因为  天呐
because, oh, my God!
谁会想的到  有一天...
Who would've thought that someday...
钱德勒·宾会买个抽屉给我
Chandler Bing would buy me a drawer?
我可想不到
Well, not me.
但事情既然发生了  就得更进一步
But that's what's happened. And there's more.
我们应该去旅行
We should take a trip.
应该吗
We should?
我们是情侣  情侣就该这样
Yep, we're a couple, and that's what couples do.
我还要去见你爸妈
And I wanna meet your parents.
我们应该跟你爸妈一起去旅行
We should take a trip with your parents!
我想不用了  因为你已经快把我搞迷糊了
I don't think we need to because you're tripping me out right now!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我很好
I am.
我真的很好  真是太不可思议了
I actually am! I mean this is amazing.
我一生都在害怕这个时刻
My entire life, I have feared this place.
但事到临头好像也没什么大不了
And now that I'm here, it's like, what was the big deal?
或许就算我说  "我们同居吧"
I mean, I could probably say, "Let's move in together, "
我还是能接受得了
and I'd be okay.
你可能想跟我一起住吗
You probably want us to move in together?
-我竟然不害怕  -是啊  但我怕了
- lt doesn't scare me! - Yeah, well it scares me!
我还没离婚呢
I'm not even divorced yet!
钱德勒  你只是邀请我来吃意大利面
Chandler. You know, you just invited me over here for pasta,
而现在你突然提到要住在一起的事
and all of the sudden you're talking about moving in together.
我其实还不是很饿
And I wasn't even that hungry.
话说时间有点晚了  我最好先...
You know what? It's getting really late, and I should just...
别走  我吓着你了  我说太多了
Oh, No, don't go! I've scared you! I've said too much!
对于爱情  我是无药可救的笨拙
I'm hopeless and awkward
却又充满渴望
and desperate for love!
珍妮斯  是我
Hey, Janice, it's me.
我只是想在去街上追你之前
Yeah, I, I just wanted to apologize in advance
先跟你道歉
for having chased you down the street.
宝贝  吃点这个  你会好受点
Here you go, honey. This will help.
我终于追上了她  然后她说...
So I finally catched up to her and she says
这段感情发展太快  我们得放慢脚步
this relationship's going too fast and we have to slow down.
这样绝不是好现象
That is never good.
于是我就变得...
Then I got all...
空虚又黏人
needy and clingy.
等等  或许不算太糟  你们怎么结束的
Wait a minute. Maybe it's not so bad. How did you leave it?
她说她会再打给我
She said she'd call me.
天呐
Oh, God.
欢迎来到隧道我们这头
Welcome to our side of the tunnel.
对了  这个冰淇淋难吃死了
This ice cream tastes like crap, by the way.
因为这是低卡无奶豆浆制的冒牌货
Well, that's that low-cal-nondairy-soymilk junk.
真货要留到实在无法挽留了再吃
We sort of, we save the real stuff for the truly terminal cases.
如果一直这么糟
You know, when you're getting screwed over all the time,
就给他换成低脂的
you gotta switch to low fat.
就这么定了
Yeah, you do.
你觉得还有挽留的机会
You don't think I'm terminal?
当然有机会  只是要防止事情恶化
Not at all. You're not terminal. We just need some damage control.
-好  我该打电话给她吗?  -不
- Okay, okay. Should I call her? - No.
这段时间很重要
Very critical time, right now.
一旦你发现自己的双手又伸向了电话...
If you feel yourself reaching for that phone...
你就去买鞋子  不然就洗个泡泡浴
you go shoe shopping, you get your butt in a bubble bath.
你若希望她回来  就给我表现得冷漠点
If you want her back, you have got to start acting aloof.
她必须知道你并不空虚
She has to know you're not needy.
所以你要做的就是
Right, so what you have to do is...
假装不经意地碰到她
you have to accidentally run into her on purpose...
然后表现得很冷漠
and then act aloof.
这样我就不会失去她了
So I'm not gonna lose her?
亲爱的  你可不完全是个失败者
Oh, honey, you're not a total loser.
我问的是  "我就不会失去她了"
I said, "So I'm not gonna lose her?"
看看谁来了
Guess who's here!
是玩具王国里最勇敢的人  本
It's the toughest guy in Toyland, Ben!
真正的美国英雄  我是美国大兵
Real American hero I'm G.I. Joe!
把芭比娃娃放下  把芭比娃娃放下
Drop the Barbie. Drop the Barbie.
美国大兵
G.I. Joe?
你真觉得他会喜欢那玩意儿
You really think he'll fall for that?
美国大兵
G.I. Joe?
好棒  我可以玩吗
Cool! Can I play?
本  你看  这个玩具保护了美国海外石油权
Look, Ben! It's a toy that protects U.S. oil interests overseas!
加油  大兵
Go, Joe!
-菲比  你在这啊不  -你看错了  抱歉
- Phoebe, there you are! - No, it's not. Sorry.
菲比  等等  等等  菲比
But, Phoebe, wait, wait. Phoebe!
乔伊啊  我刚没认出你来...
Oh, Joey! Oh, okay! See, I didn't recognize you...
因为你穿着这条裤子
...in those pants.
我参加试镜的电视电影有什么回应吗
That TV movie I went in for, did you hear anything?
我想我应该机会很大的
I think I got a shot at it.
对  他们打来了你没有入选
Yes, they called! You didn't get it!
我是说你落选了  对不起  很抱歉
Okay? I mean, you didn't get it. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
没关系  这种事时有发生
That's okay. These things happen.
但是不应该发生的  你知道吗
But they shouldn't happen. You know what?
你这行很不好混
You're in a terrible, terrible business.
天啊  我不想成为
Oh, God. I don't want to be the person
那个让你难过的人
who makes your face look like that.
我没事的  你看
I'm, I'm okay. See?
你现在变得又难过又吓人了
Now you're sad and creepy.
-我很抱歉  我要辞职  我不干了  -不
- You know what? I'm sorry. I quit, okay, I just quit. - No.
不  你不能辞职
No, no, you can't quit!
你是我遇到过最好的经纪人
You're the best agent I ever had.
当演员被拒绝是家常便饭
Look, Pheebes, rejection is part of being an actor.
你不要看做是针对你的
You can't take it personal.
不是针对你吗
Not personal? Really?
他们说从没遇过一个意大利演员
They said they'd never met an ltalian actor
有着如此糟糕的意大利腔
with a worse ltalian accent.
他们真的这么说
They actually said that?
天啊  又是那种表情  我做不了这份工作
Oh, God, there's that face again. See? I can't do this job!
这就是为何你必须得做这份工作
No, no, this is why you have to do this job!
经纪人都说谎
Agents always lie.
艾丝特尔总是说  "他们有新想法了"
You know, Estelle just says stuff like, "They went another way."
但你这样诚实  我才能改进嘛
But this? I can use this.
我可以学一种新的腔调
I can work on a new accent.
好  若对你有帮助就好
Yeah, okay. If it helps you, okay. Yeah.
你抓不到我的  士兵
You'll never get me, Joe!
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
-钱德勒  -你好  珍妮斯
- Chandler. - Hello. Janice.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
买买东西
Just a bit of shopping.
你还好吗
How have you been?
你在装英国腔吗
Are you being British?
不  再也不会了
No, Not anymore.
你怎么来这买东西  你又不住在这一带
Why are you shopping here? You don't live in this neighborhood.
你是不是在这里等我
Were you here waiting for me?
你想的倒美
Yeah, huh.
我只是...
I'm just...
要买一点派对用的东西
... picking up some things for a party.
大麦
Barley?
什么样的派对会上大麦
What kind of party serves barley?
很抱歉  我的朋友没你朋友那么有水准
I'm sorry if my friends aren't as sophisticated as yours.
派对在哪举行
Where is this party?
就在切尔西区
Here in Chelsea.
是谁办的派对
Whose party is it?
一个女人
A woman's.
哪个女人
What woman?
切尔西
Chelsea.
好吧  这种事发生只有两种可能
OK, you know, one of two things is happening here.
你不是背着我跟别人约会
Either you're seeing somebody behind my back...
若这样你就是世界第一混蛋
which would make you the world's biggest jerk on the planet...
否则就是你假装跟别人约会
or, else you're pretending that you're seeing somebody...
那你就是可悲
which makes you so pathetic
我会当即在这麦片货架区为你哭泣
I could cry right here in the cereal aisal!
这两种男人  你想当哪一种
So which of these two guys do you want to be?
我可以当那个人吗
Can I be that guy?
我们收到了更多善意的拒绝
Okay, we got some more good rejections.
有很多地方要改进
Lots of stuff to work on.
好  说吧
Okay. Shoot.
好  那个动物园广告
Okay. Oh, the zoo commercial.
我没得到那个角色
I didn't get it?
他们说你"简直不像人类"
No, they said that you "weren't believable as a human being."
所以你可以针对这一点改进
So you can work on that.
很好
Okay.
还有呢
What else?
那些小剧场的人说你"长得好看但脑瓜子笨"
The off-Broadway-play people said that you were "pretty but dumb."
等等  不好意思  他们说的是"非常笨"
Oh, no wait. I'm sorry. That's "pretty dumb."
这没关系  真的没关系
Look, it's okay, no, no, no. Really.
听着
Look...
我很感谢你  菲比
I really appreciate this Pheebs...
但我觉得还是找回艾丝特尔比较好
but I'm gonna have to go back to Estelle.
别误会  你当经纪人当得比她好
Well, don't get me wrong. You're a better agent than she is...
但至少我跟着她
... but at least with her,
我这极蠢的脑袋还保得住
I don't want to blow my pretty dumb brains out.
是的  我能理解
Yeah, no, I understand.
-真的吗  谢谢你  -嗯
- You do? Thanks. Okay. - Yeah.
抱歉
Sorry.
-等等  -干嘛
- Wait a minute. - What?
等一下
Wait a minute.
你是不是故意编出来的
Did you make all that stuff up
这样就不用当我的经纪人了
to get out of being my agent?
被你发现了
Oh, he caught me.
我被当场揭穿了
I am so busted!
我早就这么怀疑了
That's what I suspected!
然后我只好...
And then I just, you know...
把一袋大麦丢到她身上  然后逃出了那家店
...threw the bag of barley at her and ran out of the store.
天啊  我们叫你扮冷酷  不是扮蠢材
My God, Chandler, we said be "aloof, " not "a doof."
我这次真的搞砸了  对吧
I've actually ruined this, haven't I?
这次可以吃真正的冰淇淋了吗
Is it time for the good ice cream now?
是该吃了
Yeah, it is.
一切都会好起来的
You know what? Everything's gonna be okay.
你好
Hello.
珍妮斯  你可以等一下吗
Hi, Janice! Can you hold on for a second?
好  我该怎么办
Okay, okay, what do I do?
我怎么知道  这是史无前例的
How should I know? I mean, this is totally unprecedented.
若我们做出像你一样的事
If we did what you did,
男人绝不会再打来了
a man would never call.
我知道了  假装你刚睡醒
I got it! I got it! Pretend you just woke up.
这样就会打击到她
That'll throw her off!
-迷迷糊糊的  -对  还有小暴躁
- Be sleepy! - Yes! And grumpy!
你们怎么回事  别念小矮人的名字
What are you? Stop naming dwarfs!
你好  珍妮斯
Hello, Janice. Hi.
我很高兴你打来
I'm so glad that you called.
我知道我最近的表现很怪
I know I've been acting really weird lately...
那是因为我太爱你了
and it's just because I'm crazy about you...
我就变得很蠢  又很害怕
and I just got stupid and scared...
然后还蠢了好几回
and stupid a couple of more times.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
真的
Really?
他真幸运  如果珍妮斯是男的...
He's so lucky. If Janice were a guy...
她现在已经跟别人上床了
she'd be sleeping with somebody else by now.
我也爱你
I love you too.
真是太不公平了
It's so unfair!
美国大兵  美国大兵
G. I. Joe? G. I. Joe?
我不知如何告诉你们  但是他自己选的
I don't know what to tell you guys. That's the doll he chose.
你是怎么做到的  把玩具沾糖吗
What'd you do, dip it in sugar?
美国大兵获胜  芭比娃娃出局了
Look, G. I. Joe's in, Barbie's out.
如果你们不能接受  那你们就太糟糕了
And if you guys can't deal with it, that's just your too bad.
你干嘛这么小家子气
What are you being such a weenie for?
不就有个芭比嘛  有什么大不了的
So he has a Barbie. Big deal.
你以前不也打扮得像个女人似的
You used to dress up like a woman.
什么
What?
你以前都穿妈的衣服啊
The way you used to dress up in Mom's clothes all the time?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
宽帽子  珍珠项链  小手提包
The big hat, the pearls, the little pick handbag?
好  这些都是你编出来的
Okay. You are totally making this up.
你怎么可能不记得
How can you not remember?
你还让我们叫你"碧儿"
You made us call you "Bea"?
天啊
Oh, God.
我真的从没这么欢乐过
I've literally never been this happy.
不是还有一首歌吗
Wasn't there a little song?
拜托  老天  来一首歌吧
Oh, please, God, let there be a song.
根本没有什么歌  没这回事
There was no song. There was no song.
-我是碧儿  -行了
- I am Bea... - OK.
-我喝茶...  -够了够了
- I drink tea - Okay, that's enough.
你要不要
Won't you....
你要不要...
你要不要在我身旁跳支舞
Won't you dance around with me?
我是碧儿
I am Bea...
我喝茶
I drink tea...
你要不要在我身旁跳舞...
Won't you dance around with...
罗斯
Ross?